Aleksi Vuorela

Software Engineering Student

Jyväskylä044 0711969

□ aleksii.vuorela@gmail.com

aleksivuorela.github.io

Summary

A 22-year-old dude. Passionate about learning the latest technologies and writing elegant code. Good at finding simple solutions to complex problems. I also like to develop games as a hobby.

Currently having a blast working on a IoT project with React.js and AWS for the first time! Doing my 3rd year studies in software engineering. Looking for an internship position.

Experience

Junior Game Developer

05/2016 - 07/2016

N4S@JAMK

Programming educational game for healthcare students with C# and Unity game engine. Learned the basics of working as a Scrum team in practice.

Programmer 12/2012 - 10/2014

Keski-Suomen pelastuslaitos

Programming employee timesheets with VBA in Excel.

Education

Software Engineer 2014 - ongoing

JAMK University of Applied Sciences GPA 4.37/5.00 - 164/240 ECTS

Vocational Qualification in Business Information Technology

2010 - 2013

Pohjoisen Keski-Suomen oppimiskeskus

Skills

C# and .NET

C++

Java

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

I'm also familiar with: PHP, Node.js, React.js, MySQL, Git, Scrum